I don't want to call orders the regular schedule meeting of the
Myem's facility is covered.
We'll have the invocation by Mary Susan Williams.
That's right.
Gracious God, we thank you for the city of Miami.
We thank you for our city manager, our mayor, city council members.
All of the city employees and the businesses,
and churches and families and individuals that make our city the community
that we pray for this council meeting tonight.
We ask you to give the council members wisdom and guidance
as they deliberate on the items before them.
May every decision be in the interest of our community.
We ask these things in the name of Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
I call it a religious student of the Bible that you ask the Father and the Spirit
for which it stands, why nation under God,
individuals with liberty and justice for all.
I am four public input on the paper.
I am five action atoms.
Planes.
Make motion.
Second.
Jones.
Hi.
Barn.
Don't call.
Number six.
Minutes from our June 17th.
25.
Great.
Thank you.
Second.
Jones.
Hi.
Barn.
Don't call.
Number seven.
Action Adam.
Amendment to the Miami Area Economic Development Service.
Made outside the organization contract
for the private service for fiscal year 2526.
So this is the same contract.
It's that when we met with customers.
That's the nice of me.
Any questions?
I make a motion to approve.
Hi.
Jones.
Don't call.
Hi.
All right.
Number eight potential action.
Other new business.
If any of which has risen since the posting of this agenda,
cannot be posted.
There's none.
Number nine staff reports.
Ten trustee community announcements.
Number 12.
I'm sorry.
Trust manager.
Number 12 adjourn motion.
Second.
Five.